- A ship comes stocked with...
- With what?
- With... Ties of blood!
- Okay.
- Then I have to send something starting with D.
- Yeah.
- A ship comes stocked...
- With what?
With disco!
No, you have to stock it with
important things.
What?
If you have a big ship to stock, you
want important things in it.
You don't stock it with disco!
Try again.
- Umm... A ship comes stocked then.
- Okay, with what?
With you.
EVERYTHING IS POETRY BABY
Lina, I'm on the bus now.
I don't really know why I'm writing.
I don't know what to say.
I think of you sometimes... a lot.
There's a man in front of me who
smells of sweat.
Remember when I was drunk and puked
all over your shoe?
I apologised but you just laughed and
said "Everything is poetry baby".
I bet you would call the sweaty man
poetry as well.
I just think he's gross.
I wish I didn't.
I was thinking about the
bus stop earlier.
I always walk barefoot.
I know I wear shoes.
But inside of them I'm barefoot.
I know you, what's your name?
- Elmin.
- Elmin... Lina.
Elmin and Lina...
It's weird how we've been living here
all this time...
Shopped at the same store,
sat on the same bus.
But never known each other.
There are so many people we don't know.
Even though you live next to them.
I think I understand now,
that thing you said...
Do you do this a lot?
Sometimes, when Albin isn't home.
If I feel like it.
- It's fun to create, don't you think?
- Sure.
I built a lot of LEGO when I was little.
Kind of foolish to stop when you
grow older.
For a while I was really building
a lot.
- A LEGO pro, huh?
- Yeah... "LEGO pro".
- What do you want to do?
- I don't know, a castle?
- Or apartments that these can live in.
- And then?
- A train station maybe?
- I mean later.
In life.
Oh.
- Well, I don't know.
- Difference.
That's what I want to do.
How do you mean?
I don't know, just a difference.
For me, and others.
There are so many people we never meet.
We should take care of those we do.
And make a difference for each other.
But I don't know... Do you?
I'm cold, tea?